
AWS CLI Topic Guide
^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^


Description
***********

This is the AWS CLI Topic Guide. It gives access to a set of topics
that provide a deeper understanding of the CLI. To access the list of
topics from the command line, run "aws help topics". To access a
specific topic from the command line, run "aws help [topicname]",
where "topicname" is the name of the topic as it appears in the output
from "aws help topics".


Available Topics
****************


General
=======

* config-vars: Configuration Variables for the AWS CLI

* return-codes: Describes the various return codes of the AWS CLI


S3
==

* s3-config: Advanced configuration for AWS S3 Commands

* s3-faq: Frequented Asked Questions for Amazon S3 in the AWS CLI

