
AWS CLI Return Codes
^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^

These are the following return codes returned at the end of execution
of a CLI command:

* "0" -- Command was successful. There were no errors thrown by either
  the CLI or by the service the request was made to.

* "1" -- Limited to "s3" commands, at least one or more s3 transfers
  failed for the command executed.

* "2" -- The meaning of this return code depends on the command being
  run.

  The primary meaning is that the command entered on the command line
  failed to be parsed. Parsing failures can be caused by, but are not
  limted to, missing any required subcommands or arguments or using
  any unknown commands or arguments. Note that this return code
  meaning is applicable to all CLI commands.

  The other meaning is only applicable to "s3" commands. It can mean
  at least one or more files marked for transfer were skipped during
  the transfer process. However, all other files marked for transfer
  were successfully transferred. Files that are skipped during the
  transfer process include: files that do not exist, files that are
  character special devices, block special device, FIFO's, or sockets,
  and files that the user cannot read from.

* "130" -- The process received a SIGINT (Ctrl-C).

* "255" -- Command failed. There were errors thrown by either the CLI
  or by the service the request was made to.

To determine the return code of a command, run the following right
after running a CLI command. Note that this will work only on POSIX
systems:

   $ echo $?

Output (if successful):

   0

On Windows PowerShell, the return code can be determined by running:

   > echo $lastexitcode

Output (if successful):

   0

On Windows Command Prompt, the return code can be determined by
running:

   > echo %errorlevel%

Output (if successful):

   0

