
Usage:   
  pip install [options] <requirement specifier> [package-index-options] ...
  pip install [options] -r <requirements file> [package-index-options] ...
  pip install [options] [-e] <vcs project url> ...
  pip install [options] [-e] <local project path> ...
  pip install [options] <archive url/path> ...

Description:
  Install packages from:
  
  - PyPI (and other indexes) using requirement specifiers.
  - VCS project urls.
  - Local project directories.
  - Local or remote source archives.
  
  pip also supports installing from "requirements files", which provide
  an easy way to specify a whole environment to be installed.

Install Options:
  -r, --requirement <file>    Install from the given requirements file. This
                              option can be used multiple times.
  -c, --constraint <file>     Constrain versions using the given constraints
                              file. This option can be used multiple times.
  --no-deps                   Don't install package dependencies.
  --pre                       Include pre-release and development versions. By
                              default, pip only finds stable versions.
  -e, --editable <path/url>   Install a project in editable mode (i.e.
                              setuptools "develop mode") from a local project
                              path or a VCS url.
  -t, --target <dir>          Install packages into <dir>. By default this
                              will not replace existing files/folders in
                              <dir>. Use --upgrade to replace existing
                              packages in <dir> with new versions.
  --user                      Install to the Python user install directory for
                              your platform. Typically ~/.local/, or
                              %APPDATA%\Python on Windows. (See the Python
                              documentation for site.USER_BASE for full
                              details.)
  --root <dir>                Install everything relative to this alternate
                              root directory.
  --prefix <dir>              Installation prefix where lib, bin and other
                              top-level folders are placed
  -b, --build <dir>           Directory to unpack packages into and build in.
                              Note that an initial build still takes place in
                              a temporary directory. The location of temporary
                              directories can be controlled by setting the
                              TMPDIR environment variable (TEMP on Windows)
                              appropriately. When passed, build directories
                              are not cleaned in case of failures.
  --src <dir>                 Directory to check out editable projects into.
                              The default in a virtualenv is "<venv
                              path>/src". The default for global installs is
                              "<current dir>/src".
  -U, --upgrade               Upgrade all specified packages to the newest
                              available version. The handling of dependencies
                              depends on the upgrade-strategy used.
  --upgrade-strategy <upgrade_strategy>
                              Determines how dependency upgrading should be
                              handled [default: only-if-needed]. "eager" -
                              dependencies are upgraded regardless of whether
                              the currently installed version satisfies the
                              requirements of the upgraded package(s). "only-
                              if-needed" -  are upgraded only when they do not
                              satisfy the requirements of the upgraded
                              package(s).
  --force-reinstall           Reinstall all packages even if they are already
                              up-to-date.
  -I, --ignore-installed      Ignore the installed packages (reinstalling
                              instead).
  --ignore-requires-python    Ignore the Requires-Python information.
  --no-build-isolation        Disable isolation when building a modern source
                              distribution. Build dependencies specified by
                              PEP 518 must be already installed if this option
                              is used.
  --install-option <options>  Extra arguments to be supplied to the setup.py
                              install command (use like --install-option="--
                              install-scripts=/usr/local/bin"). Use multiple
                              --install-option options to pass multiple
                              options to setup.py install. If you are using an
                              option with a directory path, be sure to use
                              absolute path.
  --global-option <options>   Extra global options to be supplied to the
                              setup.py call before the install command.
  --compile                   Compile Python source files to bytecode
  --no-compile                Do not compile Python source files to bytecode
  --no-warn-script-location   Do not warn when installing scripts outside PATH
  --no-warn-conflicts         Do not warn about broken dependencies
  --no-binary <format_control>
                              Do not use binary packages. Can be supplied
                              multiple times, and each time adds to the
                              existing value. Accepts either :all: to disable
                              all binary packages, :none: to empty the set, or
                              one or more package names with commas between
                              them. Note that some packages are tricky to
                              compile and may fail to install when this option
                              is used on them.
  --only-binary <format_control>
                              Do not use source packages. Can be supplied
                              multiple times, and each time adds to the
                              existing value. Accepts either :all: to disable
                              all source packages, :none: to empty the set, or
                              one or more package names with commas between
                              them. Packages without binary distributions will
                              fail to install when this option is used on
                              them.
  --no-clean                  Don't clean up build directories).
  --require-hashes            Require a hash to check each requirement
                              against, for repeatable installs. This option is
                              implied when any package in a requirements file
                              has a --hash option.
  --progress-bar <progress_bar>
                              Specify type of progress to be displayed
                              [off|on|ascii|pretty|emoji] (default: on)

Package Index Options:
  -i, --index-url <url>       Base URL of Python Package Index (default
                              https://pypi.org/simple). This should point to a
                              repository compliant with PEP 503 (the simple
                              repository API) or a local directory laid out in
                              the same format.
  --extra-index-url <url>     Extra URLs of package indexes to use in addition
                              to --index-url. Should follow the same rules as
                              --index-url.
  --no-index                  Ignore package index (only looking at --find-
                              links URLs instead).
  -f, --find-links <url>      If a url or path to an html file, then parse for
                              links to archives. If a local path or file://
                              url that's a directory, then look for archives
                              in the directory listing.
  --process-dependency-links  Enable the processing of dependency links.

General Options:
  -h, --help                  Show help.
  --isolated                  Run pip in an isolated mode, ignoring
                              environment variables and user configuration.
  -v, --verbose               Give more output. Option is additive, and can be
                              used up to 3 times.
  -V, --version               Show version and exit.
  -q, --quiet                 Give less output. Option is additive, and can be
                              used up to 3 times (corresponding to WARNING,
                              ERROR, and CRITICAL logging levels).
  --log <path>                Path to a verbose appending log.
  --proxy <proxy>             Specify a proxy in the form
                              [user:passwd@]proxy.server:port.
  --retries <retries>         Maximum number of retries each connection should
                              attempt (default 5 times).
  --timeout <sec>             Set the socket timeout (default 15 seconds).
  --exists-action <action>    Default action when a path already exists:
                              (s)witch, (i)gnore, (w)ipe, (b)ackup, (a)bort).
  --trusted-host <hostname>   Mark this host as trusted, even though it does
                              not have valid or any HTTPS.
  --cert <path>               Path to alternate CA bundle.
  --client-cert <path>        Path to SSL client certificate, a single file
                              containing the private key and the certificate
                              in PEM format.
  --cache-dir <dir>           Store the cache data in <dir>.
  --no-cache-dir              Disable the cache.
  --disable-pip-version-check
                              Don't periodically check PyPI to determine
                              whether a new version of pip is available for
                              download. Implied with --no-index.
  --no-color                  Suppress colored output
//=============================================================================
pip install awscli --upgrade --user
//=============================================================================